{
    "subject": "resource/New_Wet_Kojak",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_indie_rock_groups",
    "human_readable": "The subject of New Wet Kojak is American indie rock groups.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.976789653301239,
            "question": "Is New Wet Kojak a popular indie rock group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8342979550361633,
            "question": "Who are the members of New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8072941303253174,
            "question": "What type of band is New Wet Kojak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6811249852180481,
            "question": "When was New Wet Kojak formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6727213859558105,
            "question": "What genre of music is New Wet Kojak known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6316789388656616,
            "question": "Where is New Wet Kojak from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4755834937095642,
            "question": "Where can you listen to New Wet Kojak's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.412744402885437,
            "question": "What is the name of New Wet Kojak's latest album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3375806510448456,
            "question": "What are some of New Wet Kojak's most well-known songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32864445447921753,
            "question": "Has New Wet Kojak won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of New Wet Kojak is American indie rock groups.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4647_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of New Wet Kojak's most well-known songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4647_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of New Wet Kojak's latest album?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4647_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you listen to New Wet Kojak's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4647_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4647_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the band New Wet Kojak, which fits within the context of American indie rock groups."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "New Wet Kojak is not exclusively an American indie rock group as some of its members have roots in other bands from different genres such as Girls Against Boys, Soulside, and Edsel which are known for punk, post-punk, and avant-garde music respectively.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}